DEBORA CRISTINA FONTANELLA

Brazilian, 23 years old

Santa Catarina, Brazil

Phone/WhatsApp: +55 49 99930-8128

E-mail: fcristinadebora@gmail.com

Summary

I have been working as a full stack web developer for 5 years. I'm always pursuing

ways to improve my work and processes in the teams I work. I like to study and build new

things, trying to apply the knowledge in my job. I trust that the knowledge must be shared

so everyone be able to grow. Furthermore, I have good communication skills, as well as

facility to learn and adapt myself to changes.

Education:

Software Engineering Specialization

Pontífica Universidade Católica – PUC

Abr/2021 - Now

Software Engineering Bacharelor

Universidade do Contestado - UNC

Jan/2017 - Dez/2020

Computers Programming Technical Course

Centro Paula Souza

Ago/2013 - Dez/2013

Professional Experiences:

SENAC - Serviço Nacional de Aprendizagem Comercial

Role: Technology teacher

Period: Jul/2021 - Now

Activities: Planning and execution of classes about technology and software

development subjects, according to institution's demand.

Compufácil Software LTDA

Role: Full stack web developer

Period: Nov/2020 - Now

Activities: Building and maintenance of web application (SaaS) for retail companies. Applying knowledge in web development, responsive layout, databases, web service integrations, DevOps and agile methodologies (Scrum). Technologies: PHP, PostgreSQL, MySQL, JavaScript, AngularJS, Laminas Framework, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git, VueJS, Shellscript, Docker, AWS and Linux.

Inove Sistemas e Soluções Empresariais

Role: Full stack web developer **Period:** Nov/2018 - Oct/2020

Activities:

- Analysis, planning and development of web application to manage with logistic companies administrative processes, other utility applications internal and external and web services. Applying knowledge in data warehouses, web development, responsive layout, database, web services integration and agile methodologies. Technologies: PHP, PostgreSQL, JavaScript, JQuery, NodeJS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Codeigniter, Git, VueJs, Lumen, SPA, REST and SOAP.
- Customer and user support and service, including problems solving activities, training execution, planning meetings, treatment and organization of demands.
- Configuration and management of domains and infrastructure of web servers and databases.

O2 Multicomunicação

Role: Jr. Full stack developer Period: May/2017 - Oct/2018

Activities: Planning and development of websites and web applications, such as e-commerce, content management systems (CMS), ticket selling application and REST APIs. Integrations with payment gateways and marketing automation platforms. Technologies and knowledge: PHP, HTML, CSS, Laravel, Codelgniter, Javascript, JQuery, VueJs, AngularJs, Git, MySQL database, Scrum

methodology.

Desbrava Internet

Role: Internal Technical Support

Period: Feb/2015 - Feb/2017

Activities: Telephone service, e-mail and internet services support (configuration,

problems solutions and maintenance).

Inside Internet

Role: Intern

Period: Nov/2013 – Oct/2014

Activities: Websites and small web applications development using Classic ASP language and HTML, CSS and Jquery library technologies; maintenance and help

to configure Wordpress websites and graphic design.

Languages:

- Portuguese as my first language
- English as a second language
- Spanish (Intermediate)